<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Keithieopia</title>
    <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Keithieopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://keithieopia.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Footprints in the Public Domain</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2018-02-10-footprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2018-02-10-footprints/</guid>
      <description>For those that have never heard of it, Footprints in the Sand is an popular religious poem with a disputed origin ultimately resulting in a lawsuit. I had wanted to feature this beautiful poem on decorative sign, but found the ugly nature of it&amp;rsquo;s legal status to be off-putting.
After some research and legal advice, I found that two doctrines called fair-use and transformation would allowed me to use Footprints in the Sand, so long as it was my own take on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Needed to Crack Passwords, 2018 Edition</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-12-13-passwd-crack-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-12-13-passwd-crack-time/</guid>
      <description>These time ranges are valid as of 2018 for attackers that might have stolen a database from a third-party website you use.
It assumes the attacker is using a cloud platform like AWS and your password has been hashed and salted by the website. You, on the other hand, should assume the website&amp;rsquo;s security was programmed by troglodytes like the guy on the right ⟶
If the site in question does store your password securely, the time to crack will increase significantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dash of En-Dash</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-08-11-a-dash-of-em-dash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-08-11-a-dash-of-em-dash/</guid>
      <description>There are two types of people in this world: those that have a complete spice rack in the kitchen and those that have a bottle of all-purpose seasoning on the dining table. Likewise, what people call a dash is actually an en-dash, em-dash, or a hyphen. To be clear, this post has nothing to do with Mrs. Dash.
Hyphens Most of us think of a hyphen when we think of the word &amp;ldquo;dash&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Stop CVS Robocalls</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-08-10-stop-cvs-robo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-08-10-stop-cvs-robo/</guid>
      <description>Recently we&amp;rsquo;ve started receiving numerous &amp;ldquo;refill reminders&amp;rdquo; from CVS for someone we don&amp;rsquo;t know. The inexplicable part is we&amp;rsquo;ve had the same phone number for several years; these calls just started out of the blue.
The number that calls is from a specific CVS pharmacy and not a generic corporate number. We called it back trying to remove our number, but the representative couldn&amp;rsquo;t find our number in their system. We where told to call the main 1-800-SHOP-CVS instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Old Bay for Foreigners</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-03-10-old-bay-for-foreigners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-03-10-old-bay-for-foreigners/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy reading about other countries and cultures, so it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise I frequent international websites. One reoccurring misconceptions I come across is that non-Americans believe &amp;ldquo;American&amp;rdquo; means something beyond national borders.
 Understand any answers to the questions you ask are going to be highly different depending on the state and region of where the person lives
&amp;mdash; Myself, during a U.S. Q&amp;amp;A for Europeans
 For non-Americans, it&amp;rsquo;s best to think of U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a File&#39;s Creation Date in Git</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-03-09-git-file-creation-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-03-09-git-file-creation-date/</guid>
      <description>If you want to find the creation date of a file in a git repo, you can issue the below command. Replace [FILENAME] with the respective file):
$ git log -1 --format=&amp;#34;%ai&amp;#34; --reverse [FILENAME] Alternatively, if you change %ai to %ac you&amp;rsquo;ll get the date the file was committed.
Most people will point out modern filesystems like ext4 keep track of when files are created irregardless of git. Normally you can use stat to display this, but the required system calls are not implemented yet in the Linux kernel:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazis Misappropriated My Privacy!</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-02-28-privacy-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2017-02-28-privacy-quote/</guid>
      <description>Given all the renewed interest in privacy rights in the so-called Post Snowden Era, I&amp;rsquo;d thought I&amp;rsquo;d clarify a misattributed quote floating around:
 You have nothing to fear, if you have nothing to hide
 Since 2011, the phrase has been used as a common retort to privacy concerns. In recent years, privacy advocates have turned the tables attributing the quote to Joseph Goebbels, the Minister of Propaganda of Nazi Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Yes to the Dress Song</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2015-01-23-syttd-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2015-01-23-syttd-song/</guid>
      <description>My wife is a fan of the TLC show Say Yes to the Dress. Knowing my Google-fu, she gave me the task of identifying the song that plays when the brides find their dress. It proved to be pretty difficult to find online even with part of the lyrics.
It&amp;rsquo;s a single called Eternal Love by Fish n&amp;rsquo; Chips. iTunes was the only place I could find selling the song right now; here&amp;rsquo;s the link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rare Birds</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2014-06-22-rare-birds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2014-06-22-rare-birds/</guid>
      <description>In grade school, I had a teacher that played a game called Rare Birds with each of her classes. The object was to silently write down three unusual facts about yourself that where not easily guessed. Once everyone was done, the teacher walked around and collected our slips in this ridiculously looking Dr. Seuss hat.
She then would pick one from the hat to read out loud, and we had to guess who we thought the three facts belonged to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auditory Processing Disorder</title>
      <link>http://keithieopia.com/post/2014-05-26-disability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://keithieopia.com/post/2014-05-26-disability/</guid>
      <description>For all my life I have had a disability called Central Auditory Processing Disorder (CAPD). People with CAPD have great difficulty understanding what others say, especially when in noisy environments such as cafeterias, playgrounds, gyms, bars, and public sporting events.
With me, the disorder manifests itself in two different ways. In loud environments, it&amp;rsquo;s similar to having a conversation with someone on the other side of a crowded indoor basketball court.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>